

PROFILE

I have taken a nontraditional path into adulthood. Upon completion of 12th grade in 1999, I pursued a life as a laborer. I met a wide variety of personalities as I worked within food service, customer phone service, military service, and construction. Ultimately finding my way back to pursuing secondary education to tinker with electronics both physically and digitally.

There is no end to learning and I look forward to more challenges. I am typically optimistic in my approach to these challenges (

CONTACT

PHONE: 859-221-6993

WEBSITE: https://adamniggebrugge.github.io/Adam_Nigg ebrugge_Developer_Portfolio/

EMAIL: adam.niggebrugge@gmail.com

HOBBIES

Long Distance Urban Running Nintendo Fan Boy Cincinnati Pro-sports enthusiast

IVOR ADAM NIGGEBRUGGE

Electrical/Software Engineer

EDUCATION

GT Coding Bootcamp June 2021 - Ongoing Full stack developer crash course exposure. Primary Javascript solutions, ES6

New Horizons May 2020 SQL Development course, focused on language syntax and design philosophy

University of Kentucky: College of Engineering Fall 2006 – Fall 2009 Bachelor of Science; GPA 3.1; 154 Semester Hours; Major Electrical Engineering

WORK EXPERIENCE

Siemens LDA: Component Owner

Feb 2012-Present

Production engineering for ANEMA induction motors in MTO factory. Provide technical support to business, trouble shooting of manufacturing problems, delivering solutions for continuous improvement of process, procedures that support sales force and labor force.

Tata Consultancy Services: Web Developer June 2010 – Feb 2012

Developed solutions for existing code in a Java framework for webbased solutions targeting small/medium businesses abroad.

Bluegrass Community and Technical College: Math Tutor Oct 2006–June 2010

Re-enforce mathematical concepts, problem solving skills

SKILLS

- Javascript
- HTML
- CSS/Materialize
- NodeJS
- SQL